<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>My Go Journey on EM</title>
    <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Go Journey on EM</description>
    <image>
      <title>EM</title>
      <url>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 19:57:26 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is Decorator</title>
      <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/python/what-is-decorator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 19:57:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/python/what-is-decorator/</guid>
      <description>In Python, a decorator is a function or a class that is used to modify the behavior of another function or class without changing its source code. A decorator takes a function or a class as input and returns a new function or class that adds some extra functionality to the original function or class.
Decorators are typically used to implement cross-cutting concerns such as logging, caching, authentication, or performance monitoring, without having to modify the code of the original function or class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Interview Questions</title>
      <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/interview/python-interview-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:58:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/interview/python-interview-questions/</guid>
      <description>What is the difference between “is” and “==”? &amp;ldquo;is&amp;rdquo; checks if two variables point to the same object, while == checks if the objects referred to by the variables are equal.
What is a decorator? A decorator is a function that takes another function and extends the behavior of the latter function without explicitly modifying it.
How would you perform web scraping in Python? You can use the requests library or BeautifulSoup library to parse the HTML of a web page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Normal Distribution</title>
      <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/statistics/normal-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/statistics/normal-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Normal Distribution is a continuous probability distribution that is widely used in statistics, mathematics, and natural sciences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regressions</title>
      <link>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/statistics/regressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erkanmalcokcom.github.io/posts/statistics/regressions/</guid>
      <description>Regression analysis is a statistical method used to model the relationship between a dependent variable (also called the response variable) and one or more independent variables (also called predictors or explanatory variables).
Regression analysis can be used to analyze and predict the relationship between two or more variables by fitting a line or curve to the data. The goal is to find the best fitting model that explains the relationship between the variables.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
